I am making this video to say hi to my viewers and listeners in China
and also to wish them Happy New Year.
I was prompted to do so by Ms
Meng Jie Ma, a Chinese student studying in Germany, who has worked diligently to translate and subtitle a number of my videos
I've placed links to those in the description of this video
Meng Jie has also organized a number of people to work on the translations
They have a group on Weibo, which I have linked to in the description
Thanks, Meng Jie
much appreciated.
I would also like to announce that my new book "12 rules for life" will be translated into Chinese and published by Beijing Cheers books.
I don't know the publication date yet, but I will let everyone know as soon as I do.
Links to the publisher are also in the description.
I am extremely pleased to hear that my lectures are finding an audience in China and Happy New Year to everyone there.
Bye, for now.